Good morning friends,
welcome once again to Option, so today I am going to
talk
about ICICI Prudential Life Insurance, such a life insurance is
a very good company, it is an ICICI group
company, so you will get job work in it, oh
totally seen, graduates can apply
and the post of unit sales manager has been
given
[Music]
I will definitely tell you today that you will get to learn a lot from this channel, you will get to
know a lot, sir, if
you like it then let's see
about today's job, you can see
a limit has been given for withdrawing money from ATM, the
selection procedure will be photo Delhi, the
selection will be done through interview
and
you will have to give the interview and it can be totally
online or you can also be face to face, even then it will be
more than your life, to get this job you
can see some criteria given, maybe some have come out now, you should have good
communication skills, you should have, you should have, the
notification for the application has also been issued,
meaning the application form has
almost started updating  If it is second samosa
then how much plastic will be the application, if it is
not of police squad then you should
apply as soon as possible, if you want to apply
and share this video with all your friends,
maybe they too have done it and are sitting at home, so
you must do it for this too,
whatever your teaching mission is, you have
already seen the definition of what is Unit Sales
Manager, so you will see that here
a post of Unit Sales Manager is given,
Unit Sales Manager is there in many places, you are
in Kerala, you are in Lucknow and see here
you do not have Palasani, after that
upload the mobile number, it should be
within MB, it should not be more than that
and next it should be in PDF format,
so it is written here, you can see, you
can also come in the document, so here the complete